Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum I
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Program Grants, Series II
  - Korea
    - Seoul Women's University
      - proposals/grants/reports, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Sogang
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Soong Sil University
      - correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - grants/reports, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Yonsei University
      - report, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - report/correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - proposals/ YU Language Institute established in LA, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - endowment grant, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - endowment grant, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Myanmar
    - The Association for Theological Education in Myanmar
      - grants, 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - grants/reports, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Maryknoll Sisters
      - proposals/correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Myanmar Institute of Theology
      - proposal/correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Singapore
    - Trinity Theological College
      - correspondence/ designated grants, 1988-1994 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - correspondence/ designated grants, 1995-2002 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Taiwan
    - Fu Jen Catholic University
      - correspondence/grants/reports, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - correspondence/grants/reports, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - correspondence/grants/reports, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report (8 CDs), 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - National Taiwan University
      - correspondence/grant/report, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Soochow University
      - correspondence/matching grant/ building fund, 1995-1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - correspondence/designated and endowment grants, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Tainan Thelogical College
      - proposal/grant/report/correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam
    - College of Foreign Languages
      - proposals/grants/reports including summer workshops, 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - proposals/grants/reports including summer workshops, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Jo Anne Kleifgen, visiting professor file, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Robert W. Winter, visiting professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Robert W. Winter Jr., visiting professor file, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Crane House
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Hue University
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-2001 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Nicole B. Wilson, visiting professor file, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - The Institute for International Relations
      - Jennifer Carter, visiting professor file, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Katherine Cook, visiting professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Katherine Cook, visiting professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Jean Arnold, visiting professor report, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Jean Arnold, visiting professor report, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Simmons College
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - United States IndoChina Reconciliation Project
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - University of Social Sciences and Humanities
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Mary Lu Landgren, visiting professor, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Mary Lu Landgren, visiting professor file, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Peter Leonard, visiting professor file, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Intra-Asia
    - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Charles and Barbara Bickford, visiting professors
      - Payap, MIT, Satya Wacana, and Petra University, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - RUPP, Cambodia, and Satya Wacana, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - RUPP, Cambodia, and Satya Wacana, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - RUPP, Cambodia, and Satya Wacana, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Discretionary Grants
      - grant, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        Madras Christian College Fundraising Consultation
      - grants, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        Tution cost for two East Timorese medical students at Griffen Center for Health and Human Rights, University Mobility in Asia and the Pacific, International Christian University The Asian Conference on Service Learning
      - grants, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        Scholar Assistance-participation in IAMS archives grant, Taipei Ricci Institute of Taiwan grant, Church World Service Leadership Development Forum grant
      - grants, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        Christian University scholar assitance to participate in the Institute for Education Management at Harvard University, Tom Cogburn consultation with Indian Institutions
    - Episcopal Church
      - grant, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - International Partnership for Service Learning
      - grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Jesuit Conference of East Asia and Oceania
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - New York Theological Seminary
      - proposal/grant/report, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Overseas Ministry Center
      - proposal/grant/report/artist-in-residence, Thailand, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - proposal/grant/report/artist-in-residence, Thailand, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - proposal/grant/report/artist-in-residence, Indonesia, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Saint Paul School of Theology
      - grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Union Theological Seminary
      - grant/ Elizabeth Luce Moore Scholarship, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Financial Records, Series III
  - Finance and Administration Committee
    - minutes/reports/actions, 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - minutes/reports/actions, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Audit Reports
    - reports, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - reports, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - reports, 1987-1989 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - reports, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - reports, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - reports, 1993-1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - reports, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - reports, 1997-1999 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - reports, 1999-2001 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - report, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Investment Committee
    - minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 9)